(Raj:)Sorry, Papa.
- Oh, that's much better. Hi.
- Hi.
- And over here is Sheldon.
SHELDON: Hi.
(Raj:)He lives with Leonard.
Oh, that's nice. Like Haroon and Tanvir.
No, not like Haroon and Tanvir.
MRS. KOOTHRAPPALI:
Such sweet young men.
(Mrs Koothrappali:)They just adopted
the cutest little Punjabi baby.
Yeah. No, we're not
like Haroon and Tanvir.
- So are you boys academics like our son?
- Yes.
(Dr Koothrappali:)Your parents are comfortable
with limited earning potential?
- Oh, yes.
- Not at all.
(Raj:)Papa, please don't start.
What? It's just a question.
He's so sensitive.
That's my life, my friends.
Good to see you. Say bye.
(Mrs Koothrappali:)- Bye.
- Bye-bye.
DR. KOOTHRAPPALI:
Wait, wait.
(Dr Koothrappali:)Before you go, we have good news.
(Dr Koothrappali:)Put the computer down
and gather your friends.
- What is it, Papa?
- I don't see your friends.
(Howard(as they gather):)Is it just me or does web-chatting with
your clothes on seem a little pointless?